{
    "subject": "resource/Joaquin_Phoenix",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Phoenix, Joaquin Rafael",
    "human_readable": "The name of Joaquin Phoenix is Phoenix, Joaquin Rafael.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9233114719390869,
            "question": "What is Joaquin Phoenix's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8917798399925232,
            "question": "What is Joaquin Phoenix's middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8916138410568237,
            "question": "Does Joaquin Phoenix have a middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8472398519515991,
            "question": "What is Joaquin Phoenix's first name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.838291585445404,
            "question": "How many names does Joaquin Phoenix have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8291344046592712,
            "question": "Are there any famous people with the same middle name as Joaquin Phoenix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7716183662414551,
            "question": "Is Joaquin Phoenix his legal first name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45996329188346863,
            "question": "What could 'Phoenix' refer to in his name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.034481655806303024,
            "question": "Is there a connection between his first and last names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01619269698858261,
            "question": "What are some common naming conventions for actors?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Joaquin Phoenix is Phoenix, Joaquin Rafael.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5886_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between his first and last names?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5886_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What could 'Phoenix' refer to in his name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5886_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Joaquin Phoenix his legal first name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5886_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5886_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5886_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5886_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5886_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5886_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5886_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5886_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5886_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5886_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5886_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more queries!  I'm ready to analyze them based on the provided context."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis JSON response indicates that the information provided in the documents supports the triple stating that Joaquin Phoenix's full birth name is Joaquin Rafael Phoenix."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Joaquin Phoenix was born with the surname Bottom, but he later changed his name to Phoenix.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context consistently states Joaquin Phoenix's name as Joaquin Rafael Phoenix, indicating that \"Phoenix\" is his surname.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context consistently refers to his birth name as Joaquin Rafael Phoenix, not just Joaquin Phoenix. Additionally, there is mention of him transitioning from being credited as Leaf Phoenix back to his birthname Joaquin Rafael Phoenix, indicating that \"Phoenix, Joaquin Rafael\" is accurate and the simplified version omits his full given name.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}